Guide to the Dr. Huey P. Newton Foundation Inc. Collection
Department of Special Collections
- Series 5: Photographs, 5
  - Sentencing of Dr. Huey P. Newton 6/22/811981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    proof sheet plus photo of Huey within court room
  - Duplicate of Sentencing of Dr. Huey P. Newton 6/22/811981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Huey with Charles Garry (Box 2, Folder 7)
    various years and cases
  - Huey with Children from Youth Institute[1973] (Box 2, Folder 8)
    photo from Huey's 1973 birthday celebration and photo of Huey, Gwen and Elaine Brown
  - 1978 Huey Talks to the Black Student Union at Merritt1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    [negatives in box 13]
  - Santa Cruz photos (Box 2, Folder 10)
    including letter and photo from Lynn [negatives in box 13]
  - Huey at Graduating Ceremonies from Santa Cruz [1 of 3]1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Huey getting diploma, with Melvin Newton, Jessica Newton, advisor Dr. Triloki Pandey, Gwen Fountaine and other unidentified people
  - Huey at Graduating Ceremonies from Santa Cruz [2 of 3]1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Huey during ceremony, with family, friends, Charles Garry, Dr. Triloki Pandey, plus several proof sheets.
  - Huey at Graduating Ceremonies from Santa Cruz [3 of 3]1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Huey getting diploma, with Melvin Newton, Jessica Newton, advisor Dr. Triloki Pandey, Gwen Fountaine and other unidentified people [negatives in box 13]
  - Picture pamphlet contained in Huey P. Newton's Revolutionary Suicide (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Huey Newton, David Hilliard Bobby Seale, Eldridge Cleaver, Kathleen Cleaver, Gene McKinney, Melvin Newton, Fred Hampton, Geronimo Pratt, storming the Capitol in 1967, David speaking at Yale, Emory Douglas, Black Panther Youth, Sickle-cell testing, Survival Conference, supporters during trial, and speaking after Huey's release.
  - Huey in Santa Cruz after charges dropped 7/13/781978 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Duplicates of Publicity Photo of Huey (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Duplicates of Individual Photos of Huey1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Newton-Erickson Book Party [1 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Erik Erickson and Huey with unidentified people signing book "In Search of Common Ground"
  - Newton-Erickson Book Party [2 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Erik Erickson and Huey with unidentified people signing book "In Search of Common Ground" proof sheet included
  - Huey with James Baldwin (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Huey with Steve Bieko (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Herman Blake & Huey P. Newton [1 of 2]1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Huey speaking at a meeting also includes copy of "The Key" National Association of Black Manufacturers, Inc., vol. 1, no. 3, July 15, 1972
  - Herman Blake & Huey P. Newton [2 of 2]1972; 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    includes letter from Brooke and a photo from Ruth
  - Duplicates of Huey & Herman Blake1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Huey, Elaine Brown & John Lee Hooker (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Huey and Elaine Brown 1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Huey P. Newton and Shirley Chisholm (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Duplicates: Huey with Shirley Chisholm (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Huey P. Newton vs. Nate Collins (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Huey and Nate boxing
  - Duplicates of Huey P. Newton Boxing Nate Collins (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Huey with David Dubois (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Huey P. Newton and Don Freed (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Huey and David at Boston Chapter 2/7/71 1971 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Huey Newton, David Hilliard, Gene Jones, and other unidentified people
  - Huey and June Hilliard (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Huey with Joan Kelly (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Duplicates Huey with Joan Kelly (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Rising up Angry Lucy Montgomery 2-20-19711971 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Chicago with representatives of Rising Up Angry
  - Huey and Fritz Pointer1972 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Huey and Fritz Pointer [1 of 2]1972 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    [as of 3/20/97 this folder is at conservation]
  - Huey and Fritz Pointer [2 of 2]1972 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Huey P. Newton with Richard Pryor (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Huey with Bobby Rush (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Huey, Bobby and Elaine (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Huey and Bobby1971, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    also Elaine Brown and other unidentified people
  - Duplicates of Huey and Bobby 1971, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    also Elaine Brown
  - [Misc. proof sheets of Huey and other party members] 1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    includes Santa Cruz photos
  - Miscellaneous photos of Huey with unidentifiable people (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous records1976, 1978, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Santa Cruz photos, Bert Schnieder, different events, christening of infant, Chaka Macumba, [negatives in box 13]
  - Proofs of Huey and various people #2 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - photos: Huey P. Newton & others 1973 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Elaine Brown, Ericka Huggins, and other unidentified people
  - Comrades in Cadence (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Outside Central Headquarters Oct. 17, 1976 Police Harassment1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    photos of policemen with various Black Panther members
  - Children From Intercommunal Youth Institute[1971] (Box 4, Folder 14)
    one photo of graduation
  - Photos of Campaign / Voter Registration Rally (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Bobby Seale one of the speakers
  - Voter Registration Rally1972 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Distribution Office Bombing (San Francisco) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Photos of Free Angela Rally San Jose 2/14/721972 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Fania Jordan (Angela's sister) and other unidentified people
  - Group Photo of Black Panther Party Children 19721972 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - [Community Worker's Day, Arroya Viega Park]1972 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Ericka Huggins plus many unidentified people, one photo from Free Clothing Drive in Philadelphia (11/28/?)
  - Community Worker's Day - Arroya Viego Park, Oakland1972 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - End of boycott press con. 2-15-19721972 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Ron Dellums and Huey Newton also copy of newspaper article about the boycott
  - Prison Busing Program1970, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Solidad Bus Trip Spring 1970 1st Bus Trip plus later one in 1971
  - Black Survival Conference (Bobby Hutton Memorial Park) May 13, 1972 1972 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Ginger, Gwen Fountaine, Robert Park, Bryan Armour, Comrade Harrison, Georgina Walker, Dolores Huffman, Norma McClure, letter from J. Nelson [negatives in box 13]
  - Black Community Survival Conference - March 1972; Community Survival Programs Sickell Cell Anemia Testing 1972 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Comrades at Huey's trial 19671967 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Young members
  - Community Survival Programs - Bobby Hutton Mem. Park - Free food give-a-way 5/13/1972 1969, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Bobby Seale, Elaine Brown, Huey P. Newton
  - [Survival Program and Conference, San Pablo Park] 1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Emory Douglas, Elaine Brown, John Seale, Huey P. Newton, Bertha Brown, Charles Garry, James Mott
  - Duplicate: Black Panther Party Community Survival Programs [1 of 2]1972 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Bobby Seale, unidentifiable people.
  - Duplicate: Black Panther Party Community Survival Programs [2 of 2]1972 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Bobby Seale, unidentifiable people, sickle-cell testing program
  - Party Members - General [1 of 4]1971 - 1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    April Bolling, Samora Johnson, Kimero Roberts (Simba+Ruth's daughter), Oakland Community School Group 7, Bárbara Pelson. Brad Lomax, Arlene Clark, Janice Banks, Ellis White, Norma Armour, Lola Wilson, Comrades in Programs, Albert Armour, Comrades in graphics, Comrades at the CDC, Beatrice Kelly, Lorene Banks, Elaine Brow, George Robinson, Flores Forbes, Gerald Edwards, Louis Johnson, Rollin Reid, Larry Ulmer, Steve Long, Ericka Huggins, Elaine Brown
  - Party Members - General [2 of 4]1971 - 1979 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    John Crear, Dale Roscoe, Donald Cunningham, Conrades in distribution, Michael Fultz, Jonina Abron, Machael Ellis, Oakland Community School Staff, Comrades in programs, Oakland Community School Group II, ages 3-4, Oakland Community School Group V, Bennie Harris, Phoebe Allen, Gary Reid, Oakland Community Learning Center (Sunday, April 4), Elaine Brown, Huey P. Newton, Bobby Seale.
  - Party Members - General [3 of 4]1971 - 1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Cindy Butler (CDC), David Hilliard (CDC), Natalie Wilson (CDC), Rasa Huggins-Mott (Ericka's Baby), Oakland Community School Group I 21/3-3, Oakland Community School Group 8, Leilah Armour, Kenya Wilson, Gary Reid, Oakland Community School Group 6, Ashanté Henderson (CDC), Oakland Community School Group III, Cindy Douglas, Kali McCutchen (CDC), Bobby Seale, Huey Newton, Albert, Leilah, Bryan, Norma and Al Armour.
  - Party Members - General [4 of 4]1976 - 1979 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Bert Schneider, Mr. Glen with comrades from the Lampost, Oakland Community School Group IV science class, Comrades in EOC (plus Smokie), Oakland Community Learning Center, Ericka Huggins, Elaine Brown plus Central Committee under Elaine's reign
  - Central Committee under Elaine's reign (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Huey, David, June, John, Bobby Members of Central Committee Various1971 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    only photos of David Hilliard and Huey Newton
  - Fred Hampton - Chicago (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Revolutionary Memorial Services for Comrade Jonathan Jackson1971 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Huey Newton, Brenda Hall, Candi Robins, Joan Kelley
  - Comrade George Jackson1971 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Jackson in prison
  - Duplicates of George Jackson1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    photos and information about upcoming book
  - Photos of the Revolutionary Memorial Services for George Jackson [1 of 2]1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    memorial service programs, crowd scenes, service photos
  - Photos of the Revolutionary Memorial Services for George Jackson [2 of 2]1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    crowd scenes, service photos
  - Comrade Joseph Waddell, murdered - June 13, 1972, section leader North Carolina Chapter of the Black Panther Party1972 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Samuel Napier (Funeral) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - People who have left the Black Panther Party (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Community Supporters1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Callins Trial 19781978 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Huey Newton, Gwen Fountaine, Bert Schneider, Elaine Brown
  - Duplicates of Callins Trial -19781978 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Huey Newton, Gwen Fountaine, Bert Schneider
  - Huey, Bobby, Elaine, John: Bobby Rush & Herman (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Baldwin - Angela Davis dinner (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Elaine Brown1972 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    family photos
  - Elaine Brown (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Elaine Brown, Press Conference about S.A.F.E. Program, Oak. 1/3/721972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Elaine Brown and other comrades during campaign (Box 7, Folder 2)
    proof sheets with seniors
  - Elaine Brown/Dick Gregory - Washington, DC 12/1/761976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Black Panther Party Lawsuit filing
  - Elaine Brown at a Fund raiser (Box 7, Folder 4)
    proof sheets with Bert Schneider, Herb Caen, Quentin Kopp and others
  - Brown Administration Staff - Aug. 19751975, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    M. Glick, Tony Kline, Paul Halvonik, Mario Obledo, Robert Gnaizda, Alice Daniel, Fred Hiestad, Patsy Fulcher, Eileen Hernandez, Elaine Brown, Jessica Nunn, Dan Lowenstein, H. Michael Bennett
  - Eldridge Cleaver - 7/4/681968 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    speaking to rally after release from San Quentin
  - Duplicates of Eldridge (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Kathleen Cleaver (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Gwen Goodloe (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Bobby Seale1972 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Bobby Seale & Family1972 - 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Elaine Brown, Ron Dellums, photo of sickle-cell testing, Charles Garry, Artie Seale, at Black political rally [negatives in box 13]
  - Bobby Seale, Artie & Malik1973 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Bobby Seale, Artie & Malik, 19731973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Duplicate of Bobby Seale & his Family1972 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Mrs. Seale - Bobby & John's mother (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Duplicate Mrs. Seale (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Drawing of Bobby Seale in the electric chair 3/15/701970 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Bobby speaking at rally1972 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Bobby Seale & Elaine Brown - Talking to the Community Housewives, Swans 12/19/721972 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    photos plus proof sheets
  - Bobby Seale & Elaine Brown - Acorn Projects, West Oakland, Talking to the People Dec. 28, 19721972 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Bobby Seale & Elaine Brown - Stage Setting at Santa Rosa 12/31/721972 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Bobby Seale & Elaine Brown - Dec. 31, 19721972 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Duplicate of June, Bobby, Mojo Chebrooks1972 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Wisconsin State Representative Lloyd Barbee (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Duplicates of Lloyd Barbee (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Autographed photos of Stymie Beard (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - John Brown - Abolitionist (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Ron Dellums (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - W.E.B. DuBois (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Emory Douglas - Speaking1972 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Emory's Art (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Autographed photo of Aretha Franklin (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Marcus Garvey (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Patrice Lumumba (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Martin Luther King (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Malcolm X (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Father Neil - Epis Priest (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Paul Robeson (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Cecil Williams (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Carribean Trip 1974 [1 of 2]1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Huey Newton, Gwen Fountaine, Molly
  - Carribean Trip 1974 [1 of 2]1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Huey Newton, Gwen Fountaine, Molly - also includes cruise information
  - 1971 Trip to the People's Republic of China1971 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Elaine Brown, Huey Newton, Robert Bay, National Minorities Institute in Peking, Toi Peng Nursery, Anne Louise Strong grave site [negatives in box 13]
  - Duplicates of Trip to People's Republic of China 19711971 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Elaine Brown, Huey Newton, Robert Bay, National Minorities Institute in Peking, Toi Peng Nursery, Anne Louise Strong grave site, Locomotives Parts factory
  - B.P. Party trip to People's Republic of China1972 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Nanking, Institute of National Minorities Peking, Yenan, "Rainflower Hill" Nanking, Macnine Tool Factory, Shanghai, Peking, Cotton Mill
  - Huey in Copenhagen 1973 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Huey Newton, Robert Bay, Gwen Fountain, Jorgen Dragsdahl, also in Sweden, Publication "International Bulletin SF" included [Socialistisk Folkeparti, Denmark]
  - Duplicates of France Trip (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Lebanon Photos #2 [1 of 2]1980 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Huey Newton, Gwen Fountaine, Molly, unidentifiable people, scenes of the area
  - Lebanon Photos #2 [2 of 2]1980 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Huey Newton, Gwen Fountaine, Molly, unidentifiable people, hospital conditions, scenes of the area
  - Lebanon (Photos)1980 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Yassar Arafat, Huey Newton, Gwen Fountaine, Molly, conditions of the area
  - Lebanon Trip (duplicates)1980 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Huey Newton, Gwen Fountaine, Molly, conditions of the area
  - Photos of struggle in Mozambique (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Santiago de Cuba: Cuna de la Revolucion [book of photos from Cuba]1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    postcard type items
  - [Miscellaneous S.Y.D.A. Foundation]1979 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Huey Newton, Ericka Huggins, unidentifiable people
  - Proof sheets [1 of 2]1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Community Survival Program, book signing with Erik Erikson and meeting/discussion
  - Proof sheets [2 of 2]1979 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    book signing/meeting, Huey with various people, Elaine's birthday
  - General Photos [1 of 3]1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    various unidentifiable people, building plans
  - General Photos [2 of 3]1968; 1971 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    various unidentifiable people, building plans, Jim Jones
  - General Photos [3 of 3]1966; 1970; 1972; 1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Robert Allen, G. Livingston, Gwen Fountaine, Jackie Spicer (including letter)
  - [Miscellaneous]1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Huey speaking at rally, Huey in China, Huey speaking with photo of Malcolm X, Ron Dellum with unidentified group, free food at survival program
  - General Photos /unable to find folder (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Jerry Elliot, school program graduation, school gardening, Ericka Huggins [negatives in box 13]
  - [Miscellaneous Photos] [1 of 5] (Box 9, Folder 8)
    proof sheets of Huey, Gwen, Charles Garry, children [negatives in box 13]
  - [Miscellaneous Photos] [2 of 5]1972 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    photos of Huey, survival program, Elaine Brown, Huey in wicker chair, Community's Workers Day - Arroya Viego Park, Black Survival Conference, Bobby Seale
  - [Miscellaneous Photos] [3 of 5]1972; 1973 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    sickel-cell testing, children in cadence, Bobby Seale, Ericka Huggins, Huey with Arafat, Free Angela Rally, Huey and Gwen with Danish SF Group.
  - [Miscellaneous Photos] [4 of 5]1971; 1972 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Huey's high school graduation, Huey's mother and father, survival conference, funeral, Huey and Shirley Chishom, photo of posters that had been shot at,
  - [Miscellaneous Photos] [5 of 5]1972 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Community Survivial Conference
  - [Miscellaneous Panthers' Photos] 1975; 1976 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    various unidentified people, Elaine Brown, Fred Hiestand at press conference with Mr & Mrs John Huggins, Bruce Terris and Mark Lane, George Jackson
  - Proof sheets (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - [KPFA Interview]1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Huey and others at radio broadcast, Ceasar Chavez and a United Farm Workers boycott
  - Anti-war African Liberation Voter Registration Conference [1 of 3]1972 June 24 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Anti-war African Liberation Voter Registration Conference [2of 3]1972 June 24 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Anti-war African Liberation Voter Registration Conference [3 of 3]1972 June 24 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Funeral of Black Panther Party member (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - [Huey with his children] (Box 10, Folder 1)
    originally framed
  - [Young boy in sailor outfit - Huey?] (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - [Huey, Gwen, Ronnie] (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - [Young woman with 2 children] (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - [Apartments and street] (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - [Huey, Gwen and Yassir Arafat] (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - [Huey and Chinese official] (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - [Huey at graduation from Santa Cruz] (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - [Huey, Gwen and other unidentified people] (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - [Huey and other unidentified people] (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - [Huey and Gwen] (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - [Huey and unidentified man] (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - [Huey and Nate Collins] (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - [Huey preparing to box] (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - [Gwen Fountaine and 3 unidentified women] (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - [Huey and unidentified man] (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - [Two unidentified girls] (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - [Unidentified woman] (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - [Huey and Jim Jones, childrens birthday party, Huey's high school graduation photo, Huey's brother] (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - [Huey's mother] (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - [Huey with unidentified children] (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - [Christmas photo - Huey] (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - [Huey at release rally] (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - [Huey in wicker chair] (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - [Huey's children] (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - [Huey with unidentified man] (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - [High school graduation] (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - [Unidentified children] (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - [Huey with group from Denmark] (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - [Cuba?] (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - [Huey boxing] (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - [Huey] (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - [Huey at Santa Cruz graduation] (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - [Huey at Santa Cruz graduation] (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - [Huey with Bert Schneider] (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - [Huey with Bert Schneider] (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - [Huey with Bert Schneider] (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - [Huey boxing] (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Oversized photos (Othertype 12, Folder 1)
    David Hilliard, Huey being interviewed at Santa Cruz, Huey return to Burning Spear, older woman trying on shoes (possibly Community Survivial Program), Huey Newton, children from Intercommunal Youth Institute
  - Art piece by Emoryn.d. (Othertype 12, Folder 1)
  - Huey P. Newton folder #4 [negs] (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Huey's trip to France [negs] (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Santa Cruz photos [negs] (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Huey at Graduating Ceremonies from Santa Cruz [3 of 3] [negs]1980 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous records [negs]1976, 1978, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Proofs of Huey and various people #2 [negs] (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Black Survival Conference (Bobby Hutton Memorial Park) May 13, 1972 [negs]1972 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Photos taken by Huey [1 of 4] [negs]1971 - 1972 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Bobby Seale & Family [negs]1972 - 1973 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - [Miscellaneous Photos] [1 of 5] [negs] (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Proof sheets [negs] (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - 1971 Trip to the People's Republic of China [negs]1971 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 1978 Huey Talks to the BSU at Merritt [negs]1978 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - General Photos /unable to find folder [negs] (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Duplicates of Individual Photos of Huey [negs]1972 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - [Negs] (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Preservation prints of mold-damaged photographs, 17 photographs: b & w: 21 x 26 cm. (Box 13, Folder 17)
    Contains photograph reproductions of images damaged by mold. Includes images of Huey P. Newton, Erika Huggins, Richard Pryor, Alec Baldwin, United Farm Workers boycott, and Black Panther Party aid projects. Copy negatives of each of these 17 photographs are available to produce duplicates.
  - George Jackson, San Quentin, 1970 Oct. 26 / Ruth-Marion Baruch1970 (Othertype 14, Folder 1)
- Series 6; Audiovisual materials, 6
  - Subseries 1: Reel-to-Reel, 1
    - Reel: from John Teeling to Charles Garry re: March 19, 1968 meeting of the County Board of Supervisors, Soquel, CA1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      includes letter from Mr. Teeling regarding the meeting and the quality of the tape
    - 10/30/69 Men's Gym Topic: "Protest, The Law, and America's Race Problem" Spkrs: Charles Garry and David Hilliard Tape 1 of 31969, 3 3/4 ips speed (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 10/30/69 Men's Gym Topic: "Protest, The Law, and America's Race Problem" Spkrs: Charles Garry and David Hilliard Tape 2 of 3 1969, 3 3/4 ips speed (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 10/30/69 Men's Gym Topic: "Protest, The Law, and America's Race Problem" Spkrs: Charles Garry and David Hilliard Tape 3 of 31969, 3 3/4 ips speed (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Berkeley Police Press Conference: The Killing of Officer Tsukamoto (Soo ka Moto) Press Conference held Thursday 8-20-60, 2:30 pm at the Berkeley Hall of Justice. Police Chief Bruce Baker answers newsmens questions. Some of the questions are not quite audible, but the answers make them pretty clear. Our apologies for the technical problems. In which Berkeley Police Chief Baker refers to"the Newtons and the Haydens" who will doubtless support the murders of the Berkeley policeman. 13 min 3 3/4 ips speed 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      duplicated on cassette 11/20/94
    - Interview with Huey Newton 8/11/70 Elsa Knight Thompson, KPFA's Program Director, interviews Huey Newton shortly after his release from prison 1970, 3 3/4 ips speed (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - For Mr. Huey P. Newton from Colin D. Edwards...Oakland...1. Item for CBC on the trial and reversal July 1970; 2. Item for CBC on Black Panther philosophy and program; 3. Message to the Black Panthers from the Popular Liberation Front for the Liberation of Palestine's girl commando officer, Leila Khaled. CBC=Canadian Broadcasting Corporation1970, 7 1/2 inces per second. full track (Box 1, Folder 7)